<?xml version="1.0"?>
<document>
	<properties>
		<title>News archive</title>
	</properties>
	<meta name="keyword" content="wicket, wicket-stuff, web, j2ee, java, dojo" />
	<body>
		<section name="News Archive">
			<p>
				Here is an overview of all Wicket related news items posted on our
				<a href="Index.html">front page</a>
				.
			</p>
			<subsection name="January 25, 2006 - Wicket-Dojo ajax-based RSS Dragon, try it now!">
				<p>
					We have just finished a demo app using some of our components. It is an Ajax-based 
					RSS reader which uses some of Wicket's beta component-level rendering functionality.
					It's not entirely stable, but it should give you a impression of what Wicket and Dojo
					are capable of. Since this application depends on a HEAD version of Wicket, getting it to work
					from the wicket-contrib-dojo-examples CVS might be a bit tricky. Therefor we have made a
					pre-compiled war file available which you can deploy in your appserver. Get it <a href="http://wicket-stuff.sourceforge.net/wicket-contrib-dojo/files/wicket-contrib-dojo-examples.war">
					here!</a>
				</p>
			</subsection>
			<subsection name="January 4, 2006 - DojoAutoUpdateHandler, try it now!">
				<p>
					We have just finished our latest component. It is an Ajax auto update handler. Since it uses Wicket's beta functionality to render a singel component, you can currently only use it with the HEAD version of Wicket.
					You can find the components when you checkout wicket-contrib-dojo from CVS.
					We've included a tutorial in our tutorial section which should get you started right away!
				</p>
				
			</subsection>
			<subsection name="November 25, 2005 - Contrib-dojo v0.3 released!">
				<p>
					We are proud to announce that version 0.3 of our library has been released.
					It now contains actual useable components. ;)
					<ul>
						<li>Fully customizable Tooltip Component (non-dojo)</li>
						<li>DojoFX Component decorators</li>
						<li>FXFeedbackIndicator component (non-dojo)</li>
						<li>FXValidationAjaxHandler</li>
					</ul>
					Check-out our tutorial section or our Tutorials or our javadoc section for more info on the components.
				</p>
				
			</subsection>
			
		</section>
	</body>
</document>